<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Context Sensitive Help (CSH) for table tx_podcast_domain_model_episode</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_podcast_domain_model_episode</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Title</label>
			<label index="subtitle.description">Subtitle</label>
			<label index="description.description">Summary</label>
			<label index="file.description">Video or audio files. Files with the same basename but other formats will be added as
				alternative source to the HTML5 tags automatically. This happenes for each episode the first time the 
				frontend is loaded. After each change of the episode, these values are recalculated.</label>
			<label index="image.description">This image will be shown as poster image.</label>
			<label index="publication_date.description">Publication Date (sort order)</label>
			<label index="duration.description">Duration will be automatically determined upon saving the episode. This happenes 
				for each episode the first time the frontend is loaded. After each change of the episode, 
				these values are recalculated.</label>
			<label index="mime.description">MIME Type will be automatically determined upon saving the episode. This happenes for 
				each episode the first time the frontend is loaded. After each change of the episode, 
				these values are recalculated.</label>
			<label index="website.description">Website will only be inserted in the XML feed</label>
			<label index="author.description">Author will only be inserted in the XML feed</label>
			<label index="keywords.description">Keywords will only be inserted in the XML feed</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Titel</label>
			<label index="subtitle.description">Untertitel</label>
			<label index="description.description">Zusammenfassung</label>
			<label index="file.description">Video oder Audio-Dateien. Gleichnamige Dateien in unterschiedlichem Format werden automatisch
				erkannt und als Alternatives Format im HTML5 Tag ausgegeben. Diese geschieht beim ersten Aufruf des Podcast 
				im Frontend und wird nach jeder Änderung an der Episode erneut berechnet.</label>
			<label index="image.description">Dieses Bild wird als Stellvertreter Bild für Videos angezeigt.</label>
			<label index="publication_date.description">Veröffentlichungs Datum (Sortierreihenfolge)</label>
			<label index="duration.description">Die Dauer der Episode wird automatisch aus der Datei berechnet. Diese geschieht 
				beim ersten Aufruf des Podcast im Frontend und wird	nach jeder Änderung an der Episode erneut berechnet.</label>
			<label index="mime.description">Die Art der Datei wird automatisch berechnet. Diese geschieht beim ersten Aufruf des 
				Podcast im Frontend und wird nach jeder Änderung an der Episode erneut berechnet.</label>
			<label index="website.description">Webseite wird nur im XML Feed ausgegeben</label>
			<label index="author.description">Author wird nur im XML Feed ausgegeben</label>
			<label index="keywords.description">Schlüsselworte werden nur im XML Feed ausgegeben</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>