<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Context Sensitive Help (CSH) for table tx_podcast_domain_model_podcast</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_podcast_domain_model_podcast</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Title</label>
			<label index="subtitle.description">Subtitle</label>
			<label index="description.description">A short description of your Podcast.</label>
			<label index="copyright.description">Copyright. If you enter YEAR, it will be dynamically 
				replaced with the current year. For Example: "© YEAR by YourCompany".</label>
			<label index="image.description">This image will be shown in the Podcast listing in iTunes and in
				the frontend of your page. Use a square image, with at least 600 x 600 pixels for iTunes listings.</label>
			<label index="itunes.description">Use iTunes optimized tags and features in the feed</label>
			<label index="categories.description">For possible iTunes categories take a look at: http://www.apple.com/itunes/store/podcaststechspecs.html#categories</label>            
			<label index="episodes.description">The episodes are listed by publication date.</label>
			<label index="author.description">Author of the Podcast</label>
			<label index="technical_contact.description">Technical contact in case there is a problem with your feed.</label>
			<label index="website.description">Website that is linked in the iTunes Podcast listing and in the frontend.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Titel</label>
			<label index="subtitle.description">Untertitel</label>
			<label index="description.description">Eine kurze Beschreibung des Podcast.</label>
			<label index="copyright.description">Copyright. Der Begriff YEAR, wird automatisch durch das aktuelle Jahr ersetzt. Beispiel: "© YEAR by Firma".</label>
			<label index="image.description">Dieses Bild wird auf der Übersichtsseite von iTunes und auf der Webseite angezeigt. Benutze ein rechteckiges Bild mit mindestens 600 mal 600 pixel für iTunes.</label>
			<label index="itunes.description">Verwende iTunes optimierte Tags und Funktionen für den Podcast-Feed.</label>
			<label index="categories.description">Eine Liste mit möglichen iTunes-Kategorieren findet man hier: http://www.apple.com/itunes/store/podcaststechspecs.html#categories</label>            
			<label index="episodes.description">Die Episoden werden sortiert nach Publikations-Datum angezeigt.</label>
			<label index="author.description">Author des Podcast</label>
			<label index="technical_contact.description">Technischer Kontakt falls es ein Problem mit dem Feed geben sollte (iTunes).</label>
			<label index="website.description">Webseite die im iTunes Podcast verzeichnis und auf der Webseite aufgeführt wird.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>